Let's go!
movie of all time it's not my favorite but I really like it what you've
insisted that we do a show on this movie well I couldn't remember the other one
that you're talking about all right but I love this movie and I do believe it is
one of the better comedies out there already in the last 10 years okay so
today we're talking about the movie 40 year old virgin yeah what's the guy's
name the actor Steve Carell Steve Carell Steve Carell and he's better known for
his role in the TV sitcom The Office right yeah he's in The Office have you
seen the British version of The Office they're different now I think at this
point I have seen the British version it's like completely different humor in
everything yeah I think maybe they started off similar but now it's kind of
diverged do you think British humor is funnier than American humor I think it's
just different no well I think you've got to be British to really understand
real British humor I guess American one it's quite easy it's pretty
straightforward anyone can understand that you have to have a PhD to find
English humor funny I like Monty Python quite a bit yeah it's hilarious how good
why are you so surprised I don't know actually I just didn't think famous in
America yeah as being a funny movie which one do you like which ones
yeah I've seen like Brian I think the Holy Grail is probably the most popular in
America oh really my favorite is the life of Brian I do like the Holy Grail though
good okay I thought in your general
yeah just so you don't leave our listeners hanging why don't you tell us
who Monty Python is well they're a group of British comedians well they were who
went to I think they met in Cambridge or Oxford I can't remember and they set
up a sort of comedy club there and then they became really famous and did some
lots of TV sketches and yeah sketch comedy show mm-hmm and they're very
intelligent very clever comedians yeah they are no I really like it as well well
going back to our movie though that is not British nothing to do with Monty
Python 40 year old Virgin basically tells the story of a guy who is very
organized works at an electronics appliance yeah just a sweet guy he's
really sweet he's kind of awkward he's kind of socially awkward he collects like
action figures and comics right yeah and he's 40 years old but he lives by
himself and he's never had sex before that's why the movies called 40 year old
Virgin right and so the plot of the movie is his friends at work find out
and so they kind of make it their quest to help him have sex for the first time
and hilarity ensues it kind of seems like American pie or one of those movies I
don't know I've never seen that you've never seen American pie no no I'm just
where I haven't seen why haven't we're not talking about that all right all
right so and basically you start to understand why he's it's not that he is
he's not attracted to women right and he's had opportunities in the past but
he's just never happened you know but these opportunities they've been kind of
messed up yeah yeah he's a victim of circumstance he has a lot of bad luck so
why do you like this movie so much the cast I think the casting is really good
it kind of combines like the vulgar American humor maybe you can say with
with character development which is what this director is really famous for
by the end of that movie I mean you really actually have a pretty good sense
of this character and the other characters in the movie as well as his
friends and stuff and I think I can really appreciate that because a lot of
comedies these days just kind of go for really typical characters and really
predictable characters whereas this movie you kind of have a better sense of
individuality of each character okay it's something that this director is
actually really famous what is the director's name Judd Apatow and any
other movies that you've seen so yeah he's directed super bad which was really
popular that was a very popular knocked up with the same group of
characters and actors and it's similar you know I mean it's his he's been
criticized for resorting to like vulgar jokes when that plot kind of fails him
mm-hmm but it's still funny super bad was kind of like that I thought it was
funny but it wasn't right super bad so what was the one with the well having
every high school stair high school students in their tests to get alcohol
and it's about just a one night when they're so actually this movie 40 year
old version is really funny because he does his friends are really putting
effort into getting him a date to getting him to go out with girls and he
starts to do this but every time something weird or quirky happens like
there are little quirky girls in there yeah a lot of crazy girls one thing
he's also been criticized a lot is that though his male characters are really
distinctive and individualistic whereas like he presents females they're not
nearly as funny ever in any of the movies and they're just kind of like
props in the movies and it's true yeah and it's true in this movie especially I
think because it's about him trying to lose his virginity but really the most
apparent like relationships and dialogues are all between the friends
right and all of his movies tend to have that kind of buddy buddy flick
element but then there is one woman that that really stands out right he starts
kind of going right yeah this girl right the one that he ends up right we won't
give it away but yeah but he just gave away no but it's really funny you can
just remain divided so do you actually know anyone like this anyone who is
40 years old virgin and this is a virgin idea but I'm not gonna say their names
on air just in case I mean no relate to to his feelings sometimes I think this is
this is nervousness around a very controversial topic because now I think
you know every in like for example United States I think the average age at
which boys lose their virginity is like 16 and girls about same age or
something so it's like I think it's very rare to find somebody over the age of
20 who has not had I don't think that's true really really yeah yeah I would say
I mean in the United States what I said that would be much more rare I write in
the United States yeah I mean not yeah I don't think 20 because I would
understand this in more conservative countries for example in England I've
got a lot of Christian friends who just you know have to wait or what to wait
religion is a big factor in so they're a bit older like 25 26 before yeah yeah I
mean as a whole I'm sure it's younger in America but I wouldn't think it's it's
that young that's it it's a 16 year old it's quite young no it is it's very young
but I think it's getting I don't know you see kids in high school who are 16
17 years old and they already have like like a full beard and they look like
to keep mature like even girls they start to develop in a lot younger age why is
that is it the hormones I think it's the hormones it's gotta be cuz it's not
normal for a 16 year old to have like a full beard you know like I'm doing I can't
even have you actually met with a full beard I've never seen you haven't seen a
lot more kids these days with beards exactly see it really makes me mad
because I can't grow a beard but yeah can't lock his hole well you you said
you can't either I can't either but you do see them there are 16 years old they
are like I don't know six feet tall they are giant they got beards down in their
belly button they drive cars so they're pretty much adults right except for the
fact that you can't drink or vote but then you know they have their own car
they're driving around they have credit cards they have part-time jobs they have
cell phones and they text message constantly yeah it's somewhere that it's
like six the average 16 year old in America texts 30,000 characters a month
on average 30,000 care whoa on average that's just on average looks up at these
statistics apparently I do I wouldn't have any characters on average in this
probably market research that's big money no but it is true it's and it's
really interesting to see the difference between teenagers in other countries like
for example United States and maybe like China or Asian countries or maybe in
England I don't know what was your teenage days like in England in England
sexual frustration we're talking about for you
I think people in England may be like a little bit more crazy really yeah I
found that too and I visited yeah I think you went to New Key crazy why do you
think we're crazier I think you're just more liberal usually European has a
connotation of like more liberal yeah more into bad tech yeah more free yeah
more into like trance music
maybe that's just nookie
Amsterdam yeah Holland no no obviously not all Europe is like this but is there a
big difference you think from like the typical high school movie that you see
from like American movies to how the reality is in England well well these
are all stereotypes are yeah the high schools in America seem like evil places
to be sure I think that's a stereotype but they are it's not a really like that
bricks and geeks that was actually coming back to 40 El Virgin that was his
first project was the TV show freaks and geeks I said cliques oh sorry yeah
and like guns do you have cheerleaders in England no we definitely see there's a
big school pride see this this is crazy how you have cheerleader competitions and
stuff like what is that that's I don't know we don't have a sport now well I
should we have a university you can do cheerleading but really see that you
know why because you guys don't pay American football you can't have
cheerleaders at a rugby game no you can't no it seems like you would lend
itself to cheer I think probably adapt I think there's we're not really happy
chirpy as happy chirpy as you know the old Americans are Brits and more sort
of great well I for one had a lot of school pride school pride huh do you
guys feel as proud as bail about your school your high school your university
yeah you put a little little stickers on your car bumper that says I went to
such-and-such University no I joined a Facebook group saying that I went to
services I think this is very American bill what I don't know school pride yeah or
like yeah putting putting it's a curious phenomenon I was being I was being
sarcastic I'm not really into that scene but there's a lot of people that
are yeah I see it a lot of people like yeah putting on their on their car
bumpers or their rear window like such-and-such University alumni or go
Huskies yeah we have lots of hoodies in Washington wearing hoodies and stuff
yeah wearing hoodies eat of us yeah exactly right now yeah right now is the
NCAA basketball tournament go Huskies see this is another big thing right like
college sports college sports so college sports is like it's just like a
professional sport basically it's how people it's talk about it's how it's
managed everything so I don't think I don't get the salary though no yeah so
that's what I don't understand is yes the students going super nuts crazy at the
games I mean because there's fans too and maybe they have classes with some of the
guys yeah I remember the only time I ever were on a professional sports team I
would totally be one of your craziest fans Marco you would yeah I don't think
I have the stature to play any professional sport apart from you play
baseball no you play baseball there's a lot of squad baseball players I'm not
sure by the way I'm like five foot seven more or less so it's not like a
very short and squat now you're insulting me go what I don't want to mess
with my because he may be a little short tiny guy he's really strong I'm
dangerous my my fists are lethal weapon yeah so this is interesting I think we
should have another conversation soon with more questions from our listeners
because we should talk more about these cultural matters cultural matters
social matters scarlet can provide the the English insight yes yeah sure she'll
be giving a lot insight in the future about they don't like cheerleading no no
I know we don't I don't know I'm completely gonna get all these years ago
yeah we do we like cheerleading but I'm actually I've never seen it in the UK
interesting well I think that's all the time we have for today the movie is
obviously remember a movie was no it's inspired us to talk about the cultural
differences see what a great movie it is it is it's a good movie it's funny it is
I agree a little bit a little bit vulgar at I think he's he balances everything out
really well it is a little bit vulgar though yeah that's funny a little bit
oh yeah it's hilarious it's good stuff don't miss it all right guys so if you
have any other questions any doubts or any suggestions please come to our
website English pot calm see everyone there bye